Jonathan Poholarz

jmpoholarz@gmail.com | https://jmpoholarz.wixsite.com/home | Valparaiso, IN | (219)252-4895

ABOUT Seeking an Internship

Junior in Computer Science at Purdue University studying software engineering. Possesses significant experience working in team environments, using critical thinking skills, and interacting with people.

Determined to work hard, learn new things, maintain a positive attitude, and gain more real world work experience in the form of an Internship.

EDUCATION

Purdue University - West Lafayette, IN

Spring 2019

BS Computer Science

Concentration in Software Engineering, Machine Intelligence

Minor in Earth/Atmospheric Science

GPA: 3.82/4.00

RELEVANT CLASSES

Software Engineering I Software Testing

Data Structures and AlgorithmsComputer ArchitectureAnalysis of AlgorithmsSystems Programming I

Operating Systems (Currently Enrolled)

Database Systems (Currently Enrolled)

SKILLS

C | C++ | C# | Java | Python 3 | Xamarin | Windows | Linux | Android | Visual Studio

PROJECTS

upgrade – Profile and messaging system to help students find tutors; Spring 2017

Group Software Engineering project developed in Xamarin C# and NodeJS

Memedemic – Command prompt styled digital recreation of the board game Fall 2017

Pandemic; Group Software Testing project developed in C++

Waves – Tetris-style game personal project developed in C++ with SDL Winter 2017

WORK HISTORY

Teaching Assistant Aug 2017 – Present

Purdue University - West Lafayette, IN

Assists running labs by answering questions, holding quizzes, proctoring exams, and participating in online class discussion board

Lead Instructor May – Aug 2017,

iDTech Camps – Lisle, IL

Taught classes in C++, assisted directors, mentored peers, setup camp equipment, socialized with parents at events, created an engaging learning environment for students, and led student activities

ACTIVITIES

Math Tutor, CoSINE Jan 2016 – Present

Secretary, Purdue University Gamers' Group Aug 2015 – Present

AWARDS/HONORS

Dean's List Status (x4), Purdue University

Fall 2015 - Spring 2017

May - Aug 2016